so when i saw this headline 36 hours in memphis i was like oh are they are they covering um
the brutal occupation that's happening in memphis right now what 36 hours of it looked like it is
a travel piece very much catered to let's have a girlies weekend in memphis this is the kind of
that permits the ethnic cleansing happening and aids it memphis is under occupation with
the memphis safe task force it's an interagency state and federal task force with over 2 000
personnel including the national guard they have arrested over 2500 people in two months the
jails are so overcrowded that three people died in nine days basically stop and frisk on steroids
with federal checkpoints now when we see over policing first of all criminalization is a tool
of authoritarianism it always starts by criminalizing people this country has always relied on criminalizing
people in order to perpetuate slavery especially um after the civil war criminalization is also
foundational to gentrification it is forced displacement getting as many people out of
these neighborhoods as possible to bring in more colonizers facing for the new york times to do
clearly catered to white people a travel piece in the middle of ethnic cleansing that is happening
in the black and brown neighborhoods in memphis fuck you new york times not that i'm surprised i i mean
we all saw how you covered everything happening in occupied palestine so something about that as well
since the 1970s the number of um opinion pieces in the new york times about palestine only one percent
of all opinion pieces were ever written by a palestinian and that is another tool of ethnic cleansing by
taking away the voice of the people who are being impacted and and then i so i'm looking reading
this little fucking travel caption you have click the photographer it's a white guy memphis through the
eyes of white people for white people while black and brown people are living in terror fuck you